Welcome to Introduction to Artificial Intelligence.
Today we'll explore the fundamentals of machine learning.
Machine learning is a subset of AI that enables computers to learn from data.
There are three main types: supervised, unsupervised, and reinforcement learning.
Supervised learning uses labeled data to train models for prediction tasks.
Neural networks are inspired by the human brain's structure and function.
Deep learning uses multiple layers to extract features from raw data.
Natural language processing allows machines to understand human language.
Computer vision enables AI systems to interpret and analyze visual information.
Thank you for joining this AI introduction session.